<timeline>
    <segment>
        <date>August 2015</date>
        <project>
            <title>First Program</title>
            <desc>I Learned basic python using a "learn python" app. A random story generator interested me, so I tried making a python replica of bitlife</desc>
            <mediaType>img</mediaType>
            <mediaPath>assets/StoryGen.png</mediaPath>
        </project>
    </segment>
    <segment>
        <date>April 2017</date>
        <project>
            <title>First Drawing</title>
            <desc>My first ever drawing made, drawn on a simple sketchpad. I designed the character from scratch and was really happy with the results</desc>
            <mediaType>img</mediaType>
            <mediaPath>assets/Drawing.webp</mediaPath>
        </project>
    </segment>
    <segment>
        <date>June 2020</date>
        <project>
            <title>First Game</title>
            <desc>After getting a laptop for the first time, I tested Unity. Surprisingly, I found it simple and it got me hooked. This is what made me decide programming as my career</desc>
            <mediaType>img</mediaType>
            <mediaPath>assets/DungeonSeeker.gif</mediaPath>
        </project>
    </segment>
    <segment>
        <date>April 2021</date>
        <project>
            <title>First Music</title>
            <desc>I downloaded LLMS studio to learn music. From there I made BGM for a game I was developing</desc>
            <mediaType>img</mediaType>
            <mediaPath>assets/FirstMusic.gif</mediaPath>
        </project>
        <project>
            <title>First 3D model</title>
            <desc>After finding out about unity, I wanted to test myself and make a 3D model to be used in my games. Although it seemed impossible for me at first, I ended up making standard quality models</desc>
            <mediaType>img</mediaType>
            <mediaPath>assets/FirstModel.gif</mediaPath>
        </project>
        <project>
            <title>First 3D game</title>
            <desc>Made after learning basic Vectors, Quaternions, Shader Graph, Animation, and so much more. It is the culmination of all my skills into one small project</desc>
            <mediaType>img</mediaType>
            <mediaPath>assets/First3D.gif</mediaPath>
        </project>
    </segment>
    <segment>
        <date>September 2021</date>
        <project>
            <title>Trading card + Board game concept</title>
            <desc>A game that runs like a card game, energy systems, attack values, defense values and so much more. The only difference is that rather than attacking directly, the cards are use to summon on the board. Every turn, the player has a relative amount of energy which can be used to use cards or move units on the board. The goal of the game is to block all enemy spawn points (not yet implemented in prototype)</desc>
            <mediaType>img</mediaType>
            <mediaPath>assets/CardBoard.gif</mediaPath>
        </project>
    </segment>
</timeline>